

ALI HAMEDELNEEL

Full Stack Developer

+249915334954

+249113178872

Email:aligowi358@gmail.com LinkedIn:https://www.linkedin.com/in/al i-hamedelneel-khalifa-gowi-0860251b7 Github:https://github.com/alialdwahy

ABOUT ME

Having 1 years of IT experience in Software Development Life -Cycle (SDLC) preparing Requirement . Developing the Front-end infrastructure using Dart, Flutter Framework . and Developing Back-End using JavaScript Node js and PHP Laravel .

WORK EXPERIENCE

Oasis Computer system Full Stack Mobile Developer July 2021 to Present

Freelancer Backend Developer May 2021 to June 2021

SKILLS

- · Git&GitHub
- Api Rest
- Flutter
- · Node js
- Laravel

Self-Training

Full Stack Developer

CERTIFICATIONS

Git&Github Udemy

Learn Flutter and Dart to Create Android and IOS Apps Udemy

Full Stack Mobile Application Development Udemy

Flutter with Firebase&Stripe Build shop app Udemy

Flutter&Dart the Complete Guide Udemy

programming Foundations Fundamentals LinkedIn

Complete Node js E-Commerce Udemy

PROG LANGUAGES

- Dart
- Java Script
- Php
- Java

EDUCATIONAL

2017-2021

Bachelor Degree Honors in Information Technology UNIVARSTY OF SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY

PROJECTS

Mamoon Mobile Application

Flutter mobile app for Al-Mamoon Insurance Company

Shadid Mobile Application

Flutter mobile app for Shadid Insurance Company

E-Commerce Application

Shopping Application and Web Backend App use Node js

Keyboard Application

Android Mobile App use Java

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Food Delivery Application

Flutter mobile app use in Frontend Flutter Framework and Node js for Backend

Shopping Mobile Application

Flutter mobile app use in Frontend Flutter Framework and Node js for Backend

Grocery Mobile Application

Flutter mobile app use in Frontend Flutter Framework and Laravel for Backend

Chat Mobile Application

Flutter mobile app use in Frontend Flutter Framework and Node js for Backend